<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>mypillowprice.com</title>
    <link href="https://mypillowprice.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://mypillowprice.com" />
    <updated>2019-03-13T17:13:57+06:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Sathi</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://mypillowprice.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title> baby pillow</title>
        <author>
            <name>Sathi</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mypillowprice.com/baby-pillow.html"/>
        <id>https://mypillowprice.com/baby-pillow.html</id>

        <updated>2019-03-12T16:08:53+06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/" alt="" />
                    Kinds of Toddler Pillows on The Market Before you like the best&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/" alt="" />
                <p><strong>Kinds of Toddler Pillows on The Market</strong></p>
<p>Before you like the best pick for your little one, make sure you have investigated these five kinds of it.</p>
<p>Latex: Most of the pillows are made of latex. They give great support to the neck and shoulder of the toddler. Also, another big thing is, they are hypoallergenic.</p>
<p>Foam: Different kinds of foam are used in pillows. Monopolistic foams like Memory foam could be one of the best elements you can pick for your kids. But all of them are excellent in terms of stability.</p>
<p>Fiber Fill: Man-Manufactured fibers like Polyesters are which that we called fiber-filled pillows. sometimes, actual fibers like wool is more used to make them. They are famous for producing huge softness and comfort. Another thing is, as a source of sleeping help, they are much to go.</p>
<p>Contour: Another important thing is these pillows are a mixer of memory foam and latex along with a minimum ratio poly fiber. These are particularly designed for babies who sleep on their side and back.</p>
<p>Feather and Down: Some pillows include a good amount of down. These are softer, bigger and more luxurious. Some of these are built of bird’s feather, and it's very expensive.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>1.Little Sleepy Head Toddler Pillow</strong></p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/61sHr9hnoTL._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/61sHr9hnoTL._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="baby pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/61zTOlUf9wL._SL1200_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/61zTOlUf9wL._SL1200_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="little sleepy head toddler pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/71P-3Tg4GvL._SX522_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/71P-3Tg4GvL._SX522_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="toddler pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
<p><strong>If you are looking for the perfect pillow for your toddler, that is both comfortable and chemical free.</strong><strong>Little Sleepy Head is one of the best toddler pillows out there because it has first class customer support to help you. One can occasionally arrive across a company that sells on Amazon that will proactively reach out to their buyer to ask if they are satisfied with the purchase.</strong></p>
<p><strong>What's excellent about this pillow is that it’s undoubtedly versatile. It's the perfect size for someplace from cot to the car, and your toddler will love taking this pillow everywhere they go.</strong><strong>Little Sleepy Head  is 100% hypoallergenic, which means it won't contribute to or reason allergies! This pillow is washable. Wash on cold, gentle sequence, and dry on low.This pillow is also lump-free.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Little Sleepy Head company cares about the comfort and support of every child.This surprising pillow is just the perfect size for your little one. It is so comfy that they will want to slumber with it and take it with them everywhere! Like their favorite blanket or stuffed “friend,” this Sleepy Head  pillow will be their new “must have</strong></p>
<p><strong> Spefications:</strong></p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Brand</td>
<td>Little Sleepy Head</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Binding</td>
<td>Baby Product</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Item Weight</td>
<td>6.1 ounces</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Product Dimensions</td>
<td>13 x 4 x 18 inches</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>2.toddler pillow</strong></p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/51VtToiPRVL._SL1000_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/51VtToiPRVL._SL1000_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="toddler pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/41qe5s4vuKL.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/41qe5s4vuKL-thumbnail.jpg" alt="baby pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
<p><strong>Dreamtown Kids Toddler Pillow With Pillowcase 14x19 White </strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dreamtown Kids, LLC is a company which was established based on a love of children. An excellent nights sleep for your little one means an excellent nights sleep for you! With Dreamtown Kids pillows designed with the exact fill to support most children's head and neck, as well as a soft cover, you can rest sure that they'll have the comfort they need.  Children also like having the safety of their very personal pillow and blanket when transitioning from co-sleeping to bed or bed to bed or any other combination. In case a pillow for bed, naps, daycare, traveling or grandparents house, the Dreamtown Kids Pillow with Pillowcase is the best decision for you!</span></p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/98Hl7TcMSL2E._UX970_TTW__.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/98Hl7TcMSL2E._UX970_TTW__-thumbnail.jpg" alt=" DREAMTOWN KIDS" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/51AsldoaTyL.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/51AsldoaTyL-thumbnail.jpg" alt="kids pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You will be happy to know that it will aid you a better procreator. This will share your duties and give the best care to your kid just like you do. You may wonder thinking that how a cushion can give your baby the best care. Here is the answer. “Dreamtown Kids” are approved by chiropractors. Along with being assured by the chiropractors, you will be more convinced to know that Dreamtown Kids products are made in the USA. </span>Both the pillow and the cover is a hundred percent hypoallergenic. You previously know that it is recommended by the chiropractors. It creates a large difference when you are up to a pad recommended by a chiropractor.<span style="font-weight: 400;">A pad must be hypoallergenic for your children because it is engaged in their health. When you are picking a hypoallergenic pillow for your toddler, your baby is safe from the dirt mites. And this  Pillow is able to do this a thousand times better than ordinary ones.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">There is a list of pillows for you to select for your kids. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since your baby ain’t old enough to choose things for himself, you gotta accept this choice seriously. All you have to do is experiment on the cushions available and find the best one between them.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> without doubt, you can buy from Dreamtown Kids.</span><span style="font-size: inherit;">No worries if you feel like you have selected wrong. You are getting 6 months as warranty and if you don’t like the pillow the manufacturing company is willing to return or replace. The buyer satisfaction and rating on Amazon are very high. There is nothing to wait for really. Go choose one for your toddler and experiment if all you have read till now are true or what!</span></p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Material</td>
<td>100% Cotton</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Filling</td>
<td>100% Polyester</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Age Group</td>
<td>Children</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Use</td>
<td>Bedding, Body, Neck, Nursing, Sleeping</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Product Dimensions</td>
<td>16 x 12 x 4 inches</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Warranty</td>
<td>30 days</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Return </td>
<td>Acceptable</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p> </p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1d5mbiu840"><strong>3.Little One’s Organic Toddler Pillow</strong></h3>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/7171FZMjC2L._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/7171FZMjC2L._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="little one’s pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/81MLaPA3EFL._SX522_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/81MLaPA3EFL._SX522_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="organic pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the years Little one's pillow has very improved the sleep and bedtime routines of tens of thousands of toddlers around the world. It is time for your little one to experience the conclusive support that comes just from a product tailor-made for them, well-researched and hand-crafted with excellent love.</span></p>
<p>These pillows may seem small at first. Measuring 13 in. X 18 in. But it's only in a toddler's dimension, accurate to keep their tiny head, neck and shoulders in a suitable, healthy and comfortable position while sleeping. This tiny size allows a much more comfortable and personalized sleeping experience compared to general pillows.</p>
<p>This pillow is excellent smooth organic cotton shell with kiddy design and colorful cover makes your toddler love it as the best sleeping partner. It has a different hypoallergenic poly cluster fiber filling to guarantee toddlers’ health and clean sleep.There is no risk of skin diseases as it’s free from dyes, bleaches and other chemicals. This is completely handcrafted with extra care and effort which is highly approved by the pediatricians.</p>
<p><strong>Why do parents choose this pillow?</strong> <br><strong>To get the following advantages:</strong></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Qualified products</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Really Chemical free </span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Made in the USA</span></li>
<li>totally hypoallergenic and washable</li>
<li>You can return a product for up to 30 days from the date you purchased it.</li>
</ol>
<p><br><br><br></p>
<p><strong>4.Hypoallergenic Toddler Pillow</strong></p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/81dBNzGfxL._SX522_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/81dBNzGfxL._SX522_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Hypoallergenic Toddler Pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/619EoSVSWiL._SL1200_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/4/gallery/619EoSVSWiL._SL1200_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="A Little Pillow Company (" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
<p><strong>Toddler Pillow (13"x18") Fun Designs - Machine Washable - Perfect for Toddlers, School, Travel, Napping &amp; Reading Support - Made in Virginia by A Little Pillow Company (White)</strong></p>
<p><strong> </strong>If you are looking for such a pillow that is comfortable and durability at the same time, then this product from Little Pillow Company can be a suitable option.This award product of A Little Pillow Company is here to give your little one an additional thrill with its interesting design models.This pillow Perfect for Toddlers, Travel, School, Napping &amp; Reading Support.Every pillow cover is repeated-stitched for further durability. Also for the highest quality control, we hand-stuff each one of these pillows.<br><br>At 13in X 18in ideal sized toddler pillow is also recommended by the pediatricians because it will keep your kid's neck fit by providing proper support.<br>This product is totally Hypoallergenic. It is produced in Virginia with a 100% hypoallergenic deluxe cluster fiber filling. also, a good thing is if your child has an allergy problem then it can be a good option for him as it will not cause allergies or off-gas. Its item special grade poly fiber pillow and don’t need to buy an additional pillowcase with it.This pillow is machine washable.<br><br><strong>Why do parents choose this pillow? </strong><br><strong>To get the following advantages:</strong></p>
<p>1. Satisfaction guarantee<br>2. The cover is another-Stitched for Durability<br>3. 100% Hypoallergenic<br>4. The cover is 100% cotton<br>5. Recommended by pediatricians<br>6. You can return a product for up to 30 days from the date you purchased it.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>bamboo pillow</title>
        <author>
            <name>Sathi</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mypillowprice.com/bamboo-pillow.html"/>
        <id>https://mypillowprice.com/bamboo-pillow.html</id>

        <updated>2019-03-13T17:13:50+06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/" alt="" />
                    1.Snuggle-Pedic Snuggle-Pedic Ultra-Luxury Bamboo Shredded Memory Foam Full Size Body Pillow with&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/" alt="" />
                <p><strong>1.Snuggle-Pedic</strong></p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/81nsvgzYbiL._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/81nsvgzYbiL._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Snuggle-Pedic" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/81ydOYgO9hL._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/81ydOYgO9hL._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="bamboo body pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/719Riz6PG8L._SL1024_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/719Riz6PG8L._SL1024_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/61wsXA-m2wL._SL1000_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/61wsXA-m2wL._SL1000_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
<p><strong>Snuggle-Pedic Ultra-Luxury Bamboo Shredded Memory Foam Full Size Body Pillow with Kool-Flow Breathable Cooling Hypoallergenic Pillow Outer Fabric - Fits 20 x 54 inch Body Pillow Cases &amp; Covers</strong></p>
<p>Snuggle-Pedic Ultra-Luxury Bamboo Shredded Memory Foam Full Size Body Pillow That NEVER GOES FLAT! Our Kool-Flow Soft and Luxurious, Extra Breathable Micro-Vented Cover created In The U.S.A. with 56.4 percent Polyester, 43% Viscose of Bamboo, 6 Percent Lycra that keeps you cool whole night! It's fully machine washable.</p>
<p>This is the most surprising body pillow in the whole world! I am a very sedentary person due to my job and this causes incredible back pain. Not only does this body pillow eliminate the need for those other three pillows I was using, but it is so much more comfortable and advantageous. I no longer expend half of my night wrangling all these pillows because my new body pillow is fluffier and it stays in one place for me all night long!”</p>
<p>This pillow is perfect for neck and shoulders pain recover.Refund guarantee without hassle. You can trail 120-night. 20 years of industry leading warranty.</p>
<p>Specifications:</p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Brand</td>
<td>Snuggle-Pedic</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Color</td>
<td>Natural White</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Size</td>
<td>Queen </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Manufacturer</td>
<td>Relief-Mart, Inc.</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Material</td>
<td>100% Bamboo Fiber</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Use</td>
<td>Neck, Body, Travel, Massage, Hotel, Sleeping, Bedding</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Filling</td>
<td>Memory Foam</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Return </td>
<td>Acceptable</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p> </p>
<p><strong> 2.uttu sandwich pillow |</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/71m7c2O5V7L._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/71m7c2O5V7L._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="uttu sandwich pillow |" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/71NxiN7UKL._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/3/gallery/71NxiN7UKL._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="uttu sandwich pillow |" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
<p><strong>UTTU Sandwich Pillow, Adjustable Memory Foam Pillow, Bamboo Pillow for Sleeping, Cervical Pillow for Neck Pain, Neck Support for Back, Stomach, Side Sleepers, Orthopedic Contour Pillow, CertiPUR-US</strong></p>
<p>UTTU Sandwich Pillow is 4.7in (high contour) and 3.9in (low contour) originally, remove the middle memory foam layer you get 3.5in (high contour) and 2.8in (low contour). This unique design allows it to be accurate for all kinds of sleepers (side/back/ stomach). It is the most popular pillow for sleeping in the world. These pillows used UTTU DYNAMIC FOAM, which doesn't get hard as a rock in cold weather. Most memory foams on the market, it remains balance firmness and comfortable feel all season. You will Sleep in happiness and wake up feeling refreshed &amp; recharged.</p>
<p>60% polyester and 40% bamboo made the cover, dust mite resistant and hypoallergenic, deeply breathable for air flow, cooling pillow gives a cool bedtime sleep. This memory foam Pillow cover fully removable and machine washable for easy cleaning care. UTTU Sandwich Pillow is certified by ISPA (International Sleep Products Association), CertiPUR-US and OEKO-TEX for durability, performance, and content.</p>
<p>In order to meet your high standard of sleep needs, the 3-layer adjustable height design of our pillow gives you 4 height choices which confirm excellent comfort and a good nighttime sleep.Another thing is to offer a 30-Days return Policy on items which you are not fully happy with. You can choose the option for a full refund or an exchange of the item.</p>
<p><strong>Specifications:</strong></p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Material Type</td>
<td>Memory foam</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Product Dimensions</td>
<td>7.9 x 7.9 x 14.2 inches</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Manufacturer</td>
<td>UTTU</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Cover</td>
<td> 60% polyester and 40% bamboo cover.</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Hypoallergenic</td>
<td>Positive</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Warranty</td>
<td>5-years</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Satisfaction</td>
<td>Guarantee </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Return </td>
<td>Acceptable</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>best travel pillow</title>
        <author>
            <name>Sathi</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mypillowprice.com/best-travel-pillow.html"/>
        <id>https://mypillowprice.com/best-travel-pillow.html</id>

        <updated>2019-03-11T20:00:12+06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/" alt="" />
                    1. Therm-a-Rest Compressible Travel Pillow for Camping, Backpacking, Airplanes and Road Trips&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/" alt="" />
                <p><strong>1. Therm-a-Rest Compressible Travel Pillow for Camping, Backpacking, Airplanes and Road Trips</strong></p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/gallery/91idZklbQCL._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/gallery/91idZklbQCL._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Therm-a-Rest Compressible Travel Pillow " width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/gallery/71LLUgRIQ-L._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/gallery/71LLUgRIQ-L._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Therm-a-Rest Compressible Travel Pillow " width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Therm- a -rest travel pillow is compressible and lightweight. It has filled with very soft foam. You can pack it down to very small with is easy to take for road trips, plane travel, camping, and backpacking. This Compressible Pillow is very popular and it is perfect for everyone from travelers to campers. The pillow foam is sourced from upcycled foam from pad manufacturing. Therm-a-Rest compressible travel pillow sleeping bags and quilts are also covered by our Better Sleep commitment.Comfortable pillow for backpacking, or hiking and compresses small for easy packing. Also looks great as a throw pillow between a trip.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"> When you wake up on a compressible bag or quilt, we are clear you will wake up feeling better than evermore. If you are not completely satisfied, return it within one month with the original receipt of purchase and we will give you a full refund- no questions asked</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">The super soft foam filling expands into a 4-inch thick pillow. Which gives extra comfort for your head, neck, and back support in tents, cars, planes, and other tough-to-get-comfortable places.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">When not in use you can store this pillow into its compact design suitcase. cord lock of the suitcase keeps the pillow compressed securely.</span></p>
<p>The cover is made with brushed polyester cloth, which is very comfortable for your skin. The cover is machine washable. The product is made in the USA, so high-quality guaranteed. Therm-a-Rest compressible travel pillow sleeping bags and quilts are also covered by our Better Sleep commitment. When you wake up on a Therm-a-Rest compressible travel pillow sleeping bag or quilt, we are clear you will wake up feeling better than evermore. If you are not completely satisfied, return it within one month with the original receipt of purchase and we will give you a full refund- no questions asked</p>
<p><strong>Spefications:</strong></p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Color</strong></td>
<td>Denim, Cardinal, Gray, Pistachio, Moon, Blue Heather, Lichen, Amethyst,BlueBird, Furry Camo</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Material(s)</strong></td>
<td>Brushed Polyester, Urethane Foam Fill</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Fabric</strong></td>
<td>Brushed polyester</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Country of Origin</strong></td>
<td>USA*Built of the Finest U.S. and Global Materials</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Return</strong></td>
<td>Acceptable</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Item model number</strong></td>
<td>Therm-a-Rest</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><strong> 2.camping pillow</strong></p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/gallery/51tPCIsRWNL.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/gallery/51tPCIsRWNL-thumbnail.jpg" alt="camping pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/gallery/51ztP1oRtL.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/gallery/51ztP1oRtL-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Teton Sports camp pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/gallery/81kbo6o3RHL._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/2/gallery/81kbo6o3RHL._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="best camping pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
<p><strong>TETON Sports Camp Pillow Perfect for Anytime You Travel; Camping, Backpacking, Airplanes, and Road Trips; Comfortable Pillow for Neck and Lumbar Support; You Can Take It Anywhere; Washable Pillow</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you are looking for a simple and comfortable camp pillow then this is your best friend.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Teton Sports is a resemble of a traditional pillow. The typical design of pillow and pillow case proved comfortable and supportive for most of the users.</span>This is not really that much ideal for backpacking but it is best fit for car campaign.<span style="font-weight: 400;">Teton Sports camp pillow is filled with synthetic fiber, inner shell is made with polyester and the is </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">pillowcase made of brushed flannel.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This pillow is good for car campaign and daytime napping. The large sized pillow gives you plenty of space to fit your head well. The soft flannel cloth gives comfort to your cheek without being too hot.</span>Comparing to other pillows this is heavier. If you need to carry the pillow far away from your car, then you should not choose this pillow. The weight of this pillow is ten ounce.</p>
<p>This pillow very easy to use. It does not require any setup. Just open the sack, and it is ready to use. Also, the flannel cloth is very easy to remove to hand or machine wash.The good thing about Teton Sports pillow is, it is affordable, durable and comfortable.<span style="font-weight: 400;">Bad things about this is, it is heavier and traditional design.</span></p>
<p><strong>Spefications:</strong></p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Dimensions</td>
<td>12" x 18"</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Inner Shell</td>
<td>P5 Poly Hi–Count</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Fill</td>
<td>SuperLoft Elite 4-Channel Hollow Fiber</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Outer  Shell</td>
<td>100% Brushed Flannel with Envelope-Style Opening</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Storage</td>
<td>Taffeta Stuff Sack with Drawstring Closure</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Brand</td>
<td>TETON Sports</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Colors</td>
<td>Brown | Black | Green | Grey</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pregnancy pillow review from users</title>
        <author>
            <name>Sathi</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mypillowprice.com/pregnancy-pillow-review-from-users.html"/>
        <id>https://mypillowprice.com/pregnancy-pillow-review-from-users.html</id>

        <updated>2019-03-11T19:59:56+06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/" alt="" />
                    1. PharMeDoc Pregnancy Pillow with Jersey Cover, C Shaped Full Body PillowPharMeDoc&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/" alt="" />
                <h2 id="mcetoc_1d1jfe6c10">1. PharMeDoc Pregnancy Pillow with Jersey Cover, C Shaped Full Body Pillow</h2>
<p>PharMeDoc is specialized in pillow comfort, especially for the expecting mother. It is one of the most popular among body pillows. This c-shaped pillow design is specific for supporting the discomfort of pregnancy surrounding back needs, as well as support for, hips, knees, neck, and head. Because of this innovative c shape design, it will replace the necessity of multiple pillows in bed. With the support of this great pillow, you will be able to watch television, read a book or do your office works on your computer.</p>
<p>The 62-inch length and 29-inch width that is entirely adjustable take measures this full body, slightly c-shaped pillow versatility to use at any point in your pregnancy, or even for body pillow support evermore. C-shape pregnancy pillow can help comfort you into better sleep, decrease obstacle entirely the night and helping relieve back pain connected with pregnancy. PharMeDoc C-Shape full body pillow replaces the need for up to multiple pillows. uphold your head, neck, spine, belly, back, hips, and legs.</p>
<p>C Shaped Full Body Pillow seriously is so soft and comfortable. What's great is that you can twist and fold the thing in a lot of different ways to accommodate how you are feeling &amp; how your body is changing. This pillow is a pregnancy game-changer.</p>
<p>This c-shaped full body pillow easy to clean, easy to rearrange and is incredibly soft. <br>locality this product in a number of configurations on your bed, couch, sofa, or even the floor.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1d1jgme0i0">Specifiations:</h2>
<table class="specifications">
<tbody>
<tr style="height: 45px;">
<td style="height: 45px;"><strong>Brand</strong></td>
<td style="height: 45px;">PharMeDoc</td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 45px;">
<td style="height: 45px;"><strong>Product dimentions</strong></td>
<td style="height: 45px;">61.8 x 29.1 x 5.9 inches</td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 45px;">
<td style="height: 45px;"><strong>Pillow Size</strong></td>
<td style="height: 45px;">Body</td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 45px;">
<td style="height: 45px;"><strong>Material type</strong></td>
<td style="height: 45px;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">100% Soft Jersey Knit Cotton</span></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 45px;">
<td style="height: 45px;"><strong>Item model number</strong></td>
<td style="height: 45px;">PMD-C-BP-JC</td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 41.375px;">
<td style="height: 41.375px;"><strong>Type</strong></td>
<td style="height: 41.375px;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Maternity Pillow</span></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 41.375px;">
<td style="height: 41.375px;"><strong>Fill Material</strong></td>
<td style="height: 41.375px;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cotton Blend</span></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 41.375px;">
<td style="height: 41.375px;"><strong>Color</strong></td>
<td style="height: 41.375px;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Grey, Blue, Pink, Mint Green</span></td>
</tr>
<tr style="height: 41.375px;">
<td style="height: 41.375px;"><strong>Item weight</strong></td>
<td style="height: 41.375px;">7.05 Pounds</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><strong>2.Pregnancy Pillow, Full Body Maternity Pillow with Contoured U-Shape by Bluestone, Back Support </strong></p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/717dC9XE2EL._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/717dC9XE2EL._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Bluestone Pregnancy Pillow" width="240" height="240"></a>
<figcaption class="gallery-description">You can hug it</figcaption>
</figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/81KbtzfQ3-L._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/81KbtzfQ3-L._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Bluestone pregnancy pillow feeding position" width="240" height="240"></a>
<figcaption class="gallery-description">You can feed it</figcaption>
</figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/81KqIViHkKL._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/81KqIViHkKL._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Blustone pillow reading position" width="240" height="240"></a>
<figcaption class="gallery-description">You can read it</figcaption>
</figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/91mV9WU4NhL._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/91mV9WU4NhL._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Bluestone pillow half line position" width="240" height="240"></a>
<figcaption class="gallery-description">Relaxing position</figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p>This pregnancy pillow is the only full body maternity pillow from the Bluestone. It is an exclusive item from this manufacturer. They ensured the most comfort and best price of the entire line of products. The best feature of this pillow is, it is multifunctional. You can use this as a pillow, as a bed or even as a sofa. So, basically you can sleep, you can watch TV, you can work on a laptop, or just relax while your baby is still supported elevated.<br><br>Because of the uniquely designed U-shaped generously oversized architecture, you will have support in the neck, shoulders, back and hips together all night long. And definitely, it will support your precious belly. It works like multiple pillows. You will not feel to toss and turn sides. If you are pregnant and uncomfortable you need one of these in your life. It provides support and cushion. It has good support all the way around.<br><br>This pregnancy pillow is wonderful. It allows you to sit in the living room for much longer. Also, who those side sleeper and this really helps him. It’s also pretty affordable if you look at other body pillows. 100% recommended. this pillow not only supports the tummy really well but supports you back as well. This full body maternity pillow feels like a nice down pillow and can be used for breastfeeding if that is something you are thinking about trying. Overall, this is a great product and I would say it’s a must-have for any mom-to-be.this product hugs the body and is so comfortable. The removable pillowcase is also a huge plus.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1d2ptaq7i0">Specifiations:</h2>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Brand</strong></td>
<td><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bluestone</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Model</strong></td>
<td><span style="font-weight: 400;">64-PREGN-U-WHI</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Product Name</strong></td>
<td><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pregnancy Pillow</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Function</strong></td>
<td><span style="font-weight: 400;">Back Support</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Product Dimensions</strong></td>
<td><span style="font-weight: 400;">60 x 38 x 7 inches</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Item Weight</strong></td>
<td><span style="font-weight: 400;">7.25 pounds</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Color</strong></td>
<td><span style="font-weight: 400;">White</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Filling</strong></td>
<td><span style="font-weight: 400;">Polyester Hollow Fiber</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Outer Cover</strong></td>
<td>100% Cotton</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Inner cover</strong></td>
<td>polypropylene</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Material</strong></td>
<td>100% Polyester</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Shape</strong></td>
<td> U-Shape</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Use</strong></td>
<td>Bedding,Body,Hotel,Sleeping</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Feature</strong></td>
<td>Anti-Apnea,Therapy</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>3. Hiccapop Pregnancy Pillow Wedge for Maternity</strong><br><br></p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/71RhjT0K3XL._SL1500_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/71RhjT0K3XL._SL1500_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="hiccapop Pregnancy Pillow Wedge for Maternity" width="240" height="240"></a>
<figcaption class="gallery-description">Support Body, Belly, Back, Knees</figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The unique feature of Hiccapop pregnancy pillow wedge is, it has different softness on a different side.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">One side with </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Deluxe, soft memory foam and other side has firmer support foam.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s two-sided design provides comfort to the expecting mom during all the three trimesters.</span>Proper belly support during pregnancy is very important to avoid swelling (edema) in hands, legs, and feet. You can place this pillow under your belly, behind your back or between your knees to help you feel more comfortable relaxing or sleeping. This is a versatile belly wedge, back pillow or knee pillow. It helps relieve nerve pain and leg numbness, too.</p>
<p>It has an unbelievably soft cover made with plush Velboa. Though the cover has made with super soft cloth yet it is durable and washable. Considering the little pampering that goes a long way in the 3rd trimester, we pulled out all the stops and found the best material possible.Hiccapop pillow wedge has got the world’s best air ventilation system. To keep pillow cooler they used CertiPUR-US which is free of PBDEs, TDCPP or TCEP ("Tris") flame retardants, mercury, lead, heavy metals, formaldehyde, phthalates regulated by the CPSC, and CFCs.</p>
<p>It includes its own travel bag to carry it everywhere. Because of the compact and portable size, you can take it to the bedroom to the couch to your favorite chair for napping. Oversized body pillows are usually bulky and hot. But this convenient size pillow has a very big plus in this case.</p>
<p><strong>Spefications:</strong></p>
<table style="width: 683px;">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td style="width: 342px;"><strong>Manufacturer</strong></td>
<td style="width: 340px;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">hiccapop</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 342px;"><strong>Item model number</strong></td>
<td style="width: 340px;">FBA_B01KG84CLI</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 342px;"><strong>Color</strong></td>
<td style="width: 340px;">Charcoal Grey</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 342px;"><strong>Product Dimensions</strong></td>
<td style="width: 340px;">13.2 x 15 x 4.5 inches</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 342px;"><strong>Item Weight</strong></td>
<td style="width: 340px;">11.2 ounces</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 342px;"><strong>Function</strong></td>
<td style="width: 340px;">Body, Belly, Back, Knees support</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p> </p>
<p> <strong> 4. Queen Rose U-Shaped Total Body Pillow</strong></p>
<div class="gallery"   >
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/51WK95UMaqL._SL1000_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/51WK95UMaqL._SL1000_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Queen Rose U-Shaped Total Body Pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/61WFDzBU7BL._SL1000_.jpg" ><img src="https://mypillowprice.com/media/posts/1/gallery/61WFDzBU7BL._SL1000_-thumbnail.jpg" alt="queen rose maternity pillow" width="240" height="240"></a></figure>
</div>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Queen Rose Company name has become synonymous over the years with high quality products for mom and baby to help make life both more comfortable and affordable. solidity and extra pleasurable, this unique Bionic Polyethylene filling without smelling provides comfort for side sleeping and retains fluffiness for better performance and longer use.</span></p>
<p>This pregnancy body pillow creates a support position for reading, nursing, watching TV, sleeping, and breastfeeding, therefore, this pillow can provide better sleep. A favorite for pregnant mothers and people suffering from hip or back pain, fibromyalgia, sciatica, poor posture, athletes, people in physical therapy or recovering from an injury, and anyone looking to get better sleep.Comfort and support, allergenic are now available with great designed to follow the shape of the pregnancy mom, and big "U" shaped maternity support pillow for sleeping and feeding at home.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This pillow is incredible. This is a lovely choice for pregnant mothers at any point in their pregnancy term, as well as anyone else wanted a supportive position for any kind of recovery that requires you to be positioned a certain way.  Though the loft is a bit higher, it provides good cradling support and gives well under pressure. The plush feel of the pillow cradles your body and allows you to relax without putting undue pressure on joints or embrace on your back.This pillow is also easily Removable Cotton Cover and is a neutral color to help match any decor.</span></p>
<p><strong>Spefications:</strong></p>
<table style="width: 683px;">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td style="width: 340.344px;"><strong>Manufacturer</strong></td>
<td style="width: 341.656px;">QUEEN ROSE</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 340.344px;"><strong>Product Dimensions</strong></td>
<td style="width: 341.656px;">55 x 31 x 7.8 inches</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 340.344px;"><strong>Department</strong></td>
<td style="width: 341.656px;">womens</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 340.344px;"><strong>Item model number</strong></td>
<td style="width: 341.656px;">PP-G01</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 340.344px;"><strong>Item Weight</strong></td>
<td style="width: 341.656px;">7.28 pounds</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 340.344px;"><strong>Batteries</strong></td>
<td style="width: 341.656px;">2 AA batteries required.</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 340.344px;"><strong>Size</strong></td>
<td style="width: 341.656px;">55in, <span class="selection">61in</span>  </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 340.344px;"><strong>Color</strong></td>
<td style="width: 341.656px;">Blue and Pink </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 340.344px;"><strong>Return</strong></td>
<td style="width: 341.656px;">Accept</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
